Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
5488 B
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
669 linear feet.
Correspondence, Rule books, Agreements, etc.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
SUBJECTS
Names:
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees.
Subjects:
Railroads--Employees--Labor unions--United States--Sources.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted. Please contact the Kheel Center Reference Archivist for access information.
COLLECTION ARRANGEMENT
This forms a portion of collection #5488 B. The guide to the entire collection is available here.
Series XXVII is arranged in 1 sub-series by Union file number.
Series XXVIII is arranged in 22 sub-series by Union file number.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series XXVII. NATIONAL INDUSTRIAL CONFERENCE BOARD
  - Sub-Series 239-0. National Industrial Conference Board
    - General, 1962 (Box 158, Folder 7)
      April 16, 1962-December 31, 1962.
    - General, 1961-1962 (Box 158, Folder 8)
      January 1, 1961-April 15, 1962.
    - General, 1960 (Box 158, Folder 9)
      January 1, 1960-December 31, 1960.
- Series XXVIII. 1922 CONVENTION
  - Sub-Series 242-3. 1922 Convention
    - Reporter, 1921-1922 (Box 158, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 242-4. 1922 Convention
    - Laws Committee, 1921-1922 (Box 158, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 242-5. 1922 Convention
    - Rules, 1921-1922 (Box 158, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 242-6. 1922 Convention
    - Officers' Salaries, 1921-1922 (Box 158, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 242-7. 1922 Convention
    - Resolutions Committee, 1921-1922 (Box 158, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 242-8. 1922 Convention
    - Ritual, 1921-1922 (Box 158, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 242-9. 1922 Convention
    - Local Arrangements, 1921-1922 (Box 158, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 242-10. 1922 Convention
    - Reports of Grand Lodge Officers, 1922 (Box 158, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 242-11. 1922 Convention
    - Mileage, 1921-1922 (Box 158, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 242-12. 1922 Convention
    - Credentials, 1921-1922 (Box 158, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 242-13. 1922 Convention
    - Delegates and Alternates, 1921-1922 (Box 158, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 242-14. 1922 Convention
    - Grand Lodge Officers, 1921-1922 (Box 158, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 242-15. 1922 Convention
    - Pullman Company Rates, 1921-1922 (Box 158, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 242-16. 1922 Convention
    - Hotel Accommodations, 1922 (Box 158, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 242-17. 1922 Convention
    - Labor, 1922 (Box 158, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 242-18. 1922 Convention
    - Conference of Grand Lodge Officers, 1922 (Box 158, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 242-19. 1922 Convention
    - Invited Guests, 1922 (Box 158, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 242-20. 1922 Convention
    - Special Car, Cincinnati to Dallas, 1922 (Box 158, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 242-21. 1922 Convention
    - Witnesses in Appeal Cases, 1922-1944 (Box 158, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 242-22. 1922 Convention
    - Committee on Committees, 1922 (Box 158, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 242-23. 1922 Convention
    - Transportation, 1922 (Box 158, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 242-24. 1922 Convention
    - Transcripts, 1922-1925 (Box 158, Folder 31)